So now that we've played Avatar's movie trailer, here's your challenge.
I want you to comment out this line.
The line that shows the trailer for Avatar.
Then, I want you to create a new object.
But this time of your favorite movie.
And I want you to play each trailer instead.
Here are the instructions one more time.
Much like Toy Story in Avatar,
we want you to create a new instance or object of the class movie.
Once you've done that, we want you to play a trailer of that movie,
using the new instance or object.
And finally, we want you to share
a screenshot of your program's output on the discussion forum.
Now, in case you have a way to video record your computer screen?
Perhaps using a smartphone,
you can also share a YouTube video of your output with us.
Make sure to check this box after submitting your response on the photo.