Okay. So, here is our program design.
I'm going to start by opening a browser and playing a song.
So previously, I Googled to find out how one would open a web browser in Python.
And I discovered that there is this function called webbrowser.open.
This function takes in the link I want to open.
I just pasted a YouTube address in there.
In fact, this could have been any link you want. All right.
Let's save the program and run it.
I'm going to call it breaktime.py.
Py stands for Python.
To run it, I will click on run,
and then click on run module.
Now my hypothesis is that when we run this program,
it will open the YouTube link. Let's see.
Oh, it seems like we have an error.
Okay. It says, "There's an error in your program: EOL," whatever that means,
"while scanning the string literal."
Okay. Oh, look, Python is pointing at the error.
It seems like I missed the closing quote.
So I'm going to add that.
Let me save the program one more time and run it.
Now, I believe it will work. Another error.
When I first learned how to program,
I felt so intimidated by these errors. Look at them.
They are red and in your face,
but to make the program work,
we have to somehow get past them.
So, would you mind reading the error and telling us
what you think is the problem with this code?
Enter your responses in this box.