Okay, so we're back to the code.
And all I've done is added the translate function to our program.
So what this code is doing now is saying,
for each file or for each photo inside our folder, rename it.
Here's the old file name,
and here's the new file name devoid of any numbers.
Now my hypothesis is that if I save and run this program,
all of the photo files will be renamed and we'll see the secret message.
So let me go ahead and save it,
and run the program. Oh, wow.
That clearly did not work.
Would you mind reading through this error and telling us what you think is the problem?
Once you have a hypothesis,
feel free to enter it in the box provided.