So here's your mini project.
We want you to create your very own secret message for a friend or a loved one.
Now, the secret message could be anything from you wishing them a great day,
to you telling them how happy you are to have them in your life.
You can start by showing them the jumbled-up version of your message.
Now, we've provided some images of the alphabet in the instructor notes.
You can use them if you'd like.
Then run the program and reveal your secret message to your friend.
Your assignment is to share videos or
photos of your friends' reaction with us on the discussion forum.
Once you're done, check this box before you continue.