Now, before we write the second part of this program,
I want you to experiment with built-in functions.
Pick any one of the built-in functions or read through their documentation.
By the way, the link to this page is available in the instructor notes.
Use your chosen built-in functions in a new program.
And then, share your experiences on the forum.
You should answer questions like,
which built-in function did you actually decide to use?
What did your program do?
And what problems did you run into?
By the way, being able to read documentation and
experimenting with Python is a big part of learning how to program.
Once you've posted your responses on the forum,
feel free to check this box before you continue.