So now that we have finished designing our project, here's your assignment.
We want you to show the program we've written together to a friend or colleague.
Now, you can continue to use the profanity editor website,
which is wdyl.com, or
you can use some sort of a different internet service, like Pirate speech.
By the way, the link to this is available in the instructor notes.
While you are doing that,
we want you to use your smartphone to
record a video of the conversation with your friend or colleague.
And then, we want you to share your YouTube video with us on the discussion forum.
Make sure you check this box after submitting your responses on the forum.